[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After directing many music videos, this director made the wonderful movie Being John Malkovich and  2002s Adaptation.", "correct_answer": "Spike Jonze", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Gondry", "Gore Verbinski", "Tim Burton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This celebrity, then 15-year-old, starred in the controversial Calvin Klein underwear advertisement which featured the tagline nothing comes between me and my Calvins.", "correct_answer": "Brooke Shields", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny Depp", "Natalia Vodianova", "Kate Moss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Moulton Marston was the psychologist who invented the polygraph or lie detector. What else did he create?", "correct_answer": "Wonder Woman", "incorrect_answers": ["The Thematic Apperception test", "The IQ Test", "Behavior Therapy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Wedding Crashers, Claires boyfriend gets sick after dinner.  What did John put in his drink to make him sick?", "correct_answer": "eye drops", "incorrect_answers": ["tabasco sauce", "shoe polish", "Ex-lax"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What geographical area is the pineapple plant native to?", "correct_answer": "Brazil and Paraguay", "incorrect_answers": ["Ecuador and Peru", "Argentina and Uruguay", "Colombia and Venezuela"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the food of death in The Godfather movies?", "correct_answer": "Oranges", "incorrect_answers": ["Canoli", "Cake", "Spaghetti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Throughout the movie Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas,  the main characters Duke and Gonzo use a variety of mind-altering substances. What is the name of the drug they take, that doesnt really excist?", "correct_answer": "Adrenochrome", "incorrect_answers": ["Devils Adrenalin", "Extasy", "Devil Ether"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In music, what does andante refer to?", "correct_answer": "Moderately slow", "incorrect_answers": ["Stop", "Lively", "Very slowly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Rorschachs real name in Watchmen?", "correct_answer": "Walter Kovacs", "incorrect_answers": ["John Ogelthorpe", "Dean Sumter", "Bruce Wayne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song is playing during the infamous pool scene with actress Phoebe Cates, in the movie Fast Times at Ridgemont High?", "correct_answer": "Moving In Stereo by The Cars", "incorrect_answers": ["The Look in Your Eyes by Gerald McMahon  Kid Lightning", "Somebodys Baby by Jackson Browne", "Fast Times by Billy Squier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What method of defense do giraffes most often employ against predator attacks?", "correct_answer": "Kicking", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "They use their horns", "Standing still"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What national symbols are subject of study of vexillology?", "correct_answer": "flags", "incorrect_answers": ["seals", "national emblems", "coat of arms"]}]